What about the left twin?
왼쪽 쌍둥이는 어떻습니까?
What is his identity?
그의 정체성은 무엇입니까?
Do you have a deeper understanding of him?
당신은 그에 대해 더 깊이 이해하고 있습니까?
His thinking is advanced
그의 생각은 진보적이다
how can you guarantee that in more than a year's time
1년이 넘는 시간 안에 그걸 어떻게 보장할 수 있나요?
his thinking has not changed.
그의 생각은 변하지 않았습니다.
The organization should investigate the left twin again.
조직은 왼쪽 쌍둥이를 다시 조사해야 합니다.
Before there is an answer,
대답이 나오기 전에,
You cannot marry without permission
허락 없이는 결혼할 수 없다
This is the rule
이것이 규칙이다
Good
좋은
I will follow all the rules of the organization
나는 조직의 모든 규칙을 따르겠습니다.
old way
옛날 방식
can I
내가 할 수 있을까?
ask you a personal question?
개인적인 질문을 하시나요?
Just ask.
그냥 물어봐.
Have you ever been married
결혼한 적이 있나요?
Have you ever had a wife and children?
아내와 자녀가 있었던 적이 있습니까?
I was before
나는 전에 있었다
I'm married
나 결혼 했어
before going to the capital.
수도에 가기 전에.
My wife is from my hometown.
제 아내는 고향 출신이에요.
People from the next village.
옆 마을 사람들.
The one with big eyes and two pigtails.
큰 눈과 두 개의 땋은 머리를 가진 사람.
Many who proposed he didn't like it
그에게 제안한 많은 사람들은 그것을 좋아하지 않았습니다.
don't know why only likes me,
왜 나만 좋아하는지 모르겠어
then I took him to town,
그런 다음 나는 그를 시내로 데려갔습니다.
I started joining the labor movement
노동운동에 참여하기 시작했어요
I also know communism
나도 공산주의를 안다
then I joined the party
그럼 난 파티에 합류했어
arranged for me to work underground.
내가 지하에서 일하도록 주선해 주었어요.
But you have to hide your identity.
하지만 신분을 숨겨야 합니다.
Like this.
이와 같이.
After two years,
2년 후,
until one day,
어느 날까지,
betrayed by a traitor
배신자에게 배신당하다
The identity of our underground workers group
우리 지하노동자 집단의 정체성
and the address
그리고 주소
everything is known
모든 것이 알려져 있다
must leave immediately.
즉시 떠나야 합니다.
I rushed home.
나는 집으로 달려갔다.
But it's still too late.
하지만 아직 너무 늦었어요.
Kuomintang secret agent.
국민당 비밀요원.
And caught him.
그리고 그를 잡았습니다.
Because
왜냐하면
didn't catch us,
우리를 잡지 못했어,
in order to take revenge and vent anger,
복수하고 분노를 터뜨리기 위해
arrested family
체포된 가족
has been executed
처형되었다
people like us
우리 같은 사람들
eradicate the rebels,
반란군을 제거하고,
create information,
정보를 생성하고,
blow up a bridge?
다리를 폭파해?
The almighty
전능하신
but often times
하지만 종종
can't protect his own family
자신의 가족을 지키지 못해요
chengzi,
청지,
busy?
바쁘다?
Not busy
바쁘지 않다
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
I ask you
나는 당신에게 묻습니다
are there many flower shops in the French concession?
프랑스 조계지에는 꽃가게가 많나요?
That is true
그건 사실이야
this westerner,
이 서양인,
really like flowers.
꽃을 정말 좋아해요.
There's another mission.
또 다른 미션이 있습니다.
Not a mission.
임무가 아닙니다.
This time help me something.
이번에는 뭔가를 도와주세요.
Help me.
도와주세요.
Buy 1000 roses
장미 1000개 구매
to be sent to the commercial bank where I work.
내가 근무하는 상업은행으로 보내야 합니다.
I understand.
이해합니다.
Romance.
로맨스.
Don't make a fuss.
소란을 피우지 마세요.
Apart from roses,
장미 외에도
you help me buy candles
내가 양초 사는 걸 도와줬어
the more the better.
많을수록 좋습니다.
As soon as possible.
최대한 빨리.
This time I won't take advantage of you again.
이번에는 다시는 당신을 이용하지 않겠습니다.
I have given you a month's salary.
나는 당신에게 한 달치 월급을 주었습니다.
You guys often trick me, right?
너희들은 나를 자주 속이는구나, 그렇지?
This should also be enough
이것도 충분할 것 같아요
based on organizational investigations,
조직 조사를 기반으로,
left twin peaches in Wuhan
우한에 남겨진 쌍둥이 복숭아
been involved
관여했다
anti-Japanese activities organized by the community.
지역사회가 조직한 반일활동.
National youth.
국민청소년.
Haven't discovered his other political background yet.
그의 다른 정치적 배경은 아직 밝혀지지 않았습니다.
Agree to get married.
결혼에 동의하세요.
It's about to arrive
이제 곧 도착할 거야
run slowly
천천히 달리다
quickly chase me
빨리 나를 쫓아와
child in the Nong Tang complex
농탕(Nong Tang) 단지의 어린이
always full of energy
항상 에너지가 넘친다
later you will know.
나중에 알게 될 것입니다.
I can't even want to sleep.
잠도 자고 싶지 않아요.
Here.
여기.
Jia Ping
지아 핑
have you come home from work?
퇴근하고 집에 왔어?
Kak Li.
리 카크.
Already eaten?
이미 먹었나요?
Not yet.
아직 아님.
This beautiful girl has never seen it before.
이 아름다운 소녀는 이전에 본 적이 없습니다.
Kakak Li.
카카크 리.
This is my fiancé, Guoguo.
이 사람은 내 약혼자??, 궈궈.
Future wife?
미래의 아내?
Nona,
노나,
I'm telling you
나는 당신에게 말하고있다
if you marry Jia Ping
만약 지아핑과 결혼한다면
very lucky
굉장히 운이 좋았다
jia Ping
지아 핑
the person is good
그 사람은 좋은 사람이야
often deliver
종종 배달하다
Fish, meat,
생선, 고기,
can't, can't
할 수 없어, 할 수 없어
me today
오늘 나
have to treat you to a meal.
당신에게 식사를 대접해야 해요.
Mr. Wu.
씨. 우.
Wu, come out quickly and help.
우, 빨리 나와서 도와줘.
Kak Li.
리 카크.
Enough already.
이미 충분합니다.
Today is the first day Liuli Guoguo came to my house,
오늘은 Liuli Guoguo가 우리 집에 온 첫날입니다.
so I show my skills.
그래서 내 실력을 보여주죠.
Another day.
다른 날.
Okay.
좋아요.
Next time, Miss came to my house to eat.
다음에는 미스 씨가 우리 집에 밥 먹으러 오셨어요.
See you later, Sister Li.
나중에 봐요, 리 자매님.
Until found.
발견될 때까지.
Had reached
도달했다
here.
여기.
The second floor
2층
street
거리
Come on, please come in.
어서 들어오세요.
I noticed that you are quite popular.
나는 당신이 꽤 인기가 있다는 것을 알았습니다.
Family is much better than neighbors
가족은 이웃보다 훨씬 낫습니다.
How
어떻게
my house is not bad.
우리 집은 나쁘지 않아요.
Later, let you try the tea I made.
나중에 제가 만든 차를 드셔보세요.
Looks like you,
당신처럼 보이는데,
also mediocre.
그것도 보통.
Correct.
옳은.
Where are the traitors?
반역자들은 어디에 있습니까?
Also divided into good and bad, right?
좋은 것과 나쁜 것으로도 나뉘죠?
Unfortunately, Miss Zuo
불행하게도 Miss Zuo
I happen to be the worst.
나는 우연히 최악이다.
Do you believe it
당신은 그것을 믿습니까?
I am hungry.
나 배고파.
Good.
좋은.
I'm going to make it now.
나는 지금 그것을 만들 예정이다.
Spring noodles
봄 국수
ada tumis Xue Li Hong
아다 투미스 쉬 리 홍
can it?
그럴 수 있어?
Up to you.
당신한테 달렸습니다.
Do not hesitate.
주저하지 말고.
Sit down.
앉아.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Want to eat spicy?
매운걸 먹고 싶어?
I eat spicy or not
매운 걸 먹든 안 먹든
don't you know?
모르시나요?
I see your house is quite old,
그러고 보니 집이 꽤 낡았네요.
This wall smells
이 벽에선 냄새가 나
it's time to stick the wallpaper.
이제 벽지를 붙일 차례입니다.
Good.
좋은.
Later you choose.
나중에 선택하세요.
You help me.
당신이 나를 도와주세요.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
At my place there is no lard.
제가 있는 집에는 라드가 없습니다.
If Yang Chun noodles don't have lard, then there's no soul.
양춘면에 돼지기름이 없으면 영혼도 없습니다.
You help me get this bowl.
이 그릇을 가져오도록 도와주세요.
Message to Sis Li below.
아래는 Sis Li에게 보내는 메시지입니다.
I'm not feeling well.
난 기분이 아니에요.
I'm not familiar with him.
나는 그 사람을 잘 모른다.
one time,
한 번,
wouldn't it be familiar after two times?
두 번 하고 나면 낯설지 않을까?
Moreover,
게다가,
lard that Sister Li used
리 자매가 사용한 돼지기름
that I gave him at that time.
그 때 내가 그 사람에게 준 것입니다.
The appearance is small.
외관은 작습니다.
Quite interesting.
꽤 흥미로운.
Finally finished.
드디어 끝났습니다.
It's finished?
끝났나요?
Still old.
아직 늙었어요.
Choosing a wedding dress, choosing a day at the hotel.
웨딩 드레스 선택, 호텔에서의 하루 선택.
There are still many things waiting for us.
아직 우리를 기다리고 있는 것들이 많이 있습니다.
Regret, right?
후회하지?
I didn't say.
나는 말하지 않았다.
You didn't say?
말하지 않았나요?
Your heart must say so.
당신의 마음이 그렇게 말해야합니다.
How about you listen
들어보는 건 어때?
what am I saying in my heart?
나는 마음속으로 무슨 말을 하고 있는 걸까?
Lazy to move.
움직이기엔 게으르다.
Listen to what you say.
당신이 말하는 것을 들어보세요.
It's normal for you to be a traitor.
당신이 배신자가 되는 것은 정상이다.
Let's just go straight away.
그냥 바로 가자.
Not living in Shanghai anymore.
더 이상 상하이에 살지 않습니다.
Japanese people are everywhere.
일본인은 어디에나 있습니다.
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
Only if one day the Japanese leave,
언젠가 일본인이 떠나면
only then can we be free.
그래야만 우리는 자유로울 수 있습니다.
Tomorrow we go buy a mattress.
내일 우리는 매트리스를 사러 갑니다.
Can't sleep on the floor directly
바닥에서 바로 잠을 잘 수 없다
tomorrow you go choose curtains.
내일 가서 커튼을 고르세요.
I went to choose a bed.
침대를 고르러 갔습니다.
Okay
좋아요
soft or hard mattress?
부드럽거나 단단한 매트리스?
Mattress, you just order it
매트리스, 그냥 주문하세요
I will obey you
나는 당신에게 복종할 것입니다
Good.
좋은.
Curtain, listen to me.
커튼아, 내 말 좀 들어라.
Yes
예
I felt on the bed
침대 위에서 느꼈어
should be a little elastic
약간 탄력이 있어야 해요
It is such a coincidence.
정말 우연의 일치입니다.
As it happens.
일어나는 대로.
Here.
여기.
Eat together a little.
조금 같이 먹어요.
Have eaten above.
위에서 먹었습니다.
Unexpected.
예기치 않은.
Didn't think so?
그렇게 생각하지 않았나요?
Unexpectedly you are so brave
의외로 넌 너무 용감해
without the slightest hesitation.
조금의 망설임도 없이.
It doesn't matter if it's a grave or not.
무덤인지 아닌지는 중요하지 않습니다.
Anyway, in the end,
아무튼 결국,
buried my left twin peach blossoms.
내 왼쪽 쌍둥이 복숭아꽃을 묻었어요.
That also matches.
그것도 일치합니다.
Second Princess.
두 번째 공주.
Get me a small cup.
작은 컵 좀 갖다 주세요.
Good.
좋은.
Such a touching statement of love.
너무나 감동적인 사랑의 선언입니다.
Enjoy.
즐기다.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Sadly,
슬프게도,
in the end it won't be my turn.
결국 내 차례가 아닐 것이다.
Lu Fang
루팡
I feel
나는 느낀다
You used to misunderstand me.
당신은 나를 오해하곤 했어요.
I didn't misunderstand.
나는 오해하지 않았다.
I like you.
좋아해요.
You don't like me?
당신은 나를 좋아하지 않습니까?
So, here it is,
자, 여기 있습니다.
isn't that so?
그렇지 않나요?
Did I really misunderstand?
제가 정말 오해한 걸까요?
You used to like me too
너도 날 좋아했었지
not
~ 아니다
luFang
루팡
never mind, don't talk anymore.
신경 쓰지 마세요. 더 이상 이야기하지 마세요.
Even if there is,
있다고 해도,
you don't dare to say either.
너도 감히 말하지 못하는구나.
Your little wife
당신의 작은 아내
have power
힘이 있다
chen Jia Ping
첸 지아 핑
Don't blame me for not reminding you.
당신에게 상기시키지 못했다고 나를 비난하지 마세요.
Zhao Andan Luo Guanqun.
조안단(뤄관춘).
This time with all my might
이번에는 온 힘을 다해
to help your wedding.
당신의 결혼식을 돕기 위해.
Don't you feel something strange?
뭔가 이상한 느낌이 들지 않나요?
He just wanted to
그는 단지 원했어요
hubungan Yu Shanren ini?
후붕안 Yu Shanren ini?
It's not that simple.
그렇게 간단하지 않습니다.
Then I ask one more question.
그럼 한 가지 더 질문하겠습니다.
If...
만약에...
The Zuo twins were truly murderers.
Zuo 쌍둥이는 진정한 살인자였습니다.
Do you still dare to love and marry him?
아직도 감히 그를 사랑하고 결혼할 수 있나요?
If the person you love is a murderer,
당신이 사랑하는 사람이 살인자라면,
This question is good.
이 질문은 좋습니다.
I have to think about it carefully.
신중하게 생각해야 해요.
Married, really married.
결혼했어요, 정말 결혼했어요.
Why?
왜?
A young unmarried woman like me
나같은 젊은 미혼여성
can't choose anyone.
누구도 선택할 수 없습니다.
What killer? A spy?
무슨 살인자? 스파이?
Cannot be selected.
선택할 수 없습니다.
If you dare to marry me
감히 나와 결혼할 생각이 있다면
then I dare to marry.
그렇다면 감히 결혼하겠습니다.
According to me,
나에 따라,
Your previous tastes were too high.
이전 취향이 너무 높았어요.
I'm not good at judging,
제가 판단을 잘 못하는 편인데,
you don't understand me.
당신은 나를 이해하지 못합니다.
I really don't understand you.
나는 정말로 당신을 이해하지 못합니다.
However,
하지만,
according to my instincts,
내 본능에 따르면,
I feel
나는 느낀다
You're different from people in business.
당신은 사업하는 사람들과 다릅니다.
Trust your instincts.
너의 본능을 믿어 ​​봐.
Man,
남성,
don't tell
말하지 마세요
in women.
여성에서.
Even the closest woman,
가장 가까운 여자라도
there are some secrets,
몇 가지 비밀이 있는데,
which is kept in the heart.
마음속에 간직하고 있는 것.
Understand.
이해하다.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Enough already.
이미 충분합니다.
I also don't drink beer anymore.
나도 이제 맥주를 마시지 않는다.
Early tomorrow morning,
내일 아침 일찍,
Zhao An still wants to ask me to review the interim budget.
Zhao An은 여전히 ​​나에게 임시 예산을 검토해 달라고 요청하고 싶어합니다.
Temporary budget?
임시예산?
Kapten Zhao,
캡텐 자오,
what other big moves will you make?
또 어떤 큰 움직임을 보이나요?
Looks like a meeting.
회의인 것 같습니다.
I don't know the details either.
자세한 내용은 저도 모릅니다.
I don't even have to ask much.
별로 물어볼 필요도 없어요.
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
You...
너...
Had to change a new plan.
새로운 계획을 변경해야 했습니다.
Correct.
옳은.
How do you prepare for a special meeting?
특별한 모임을 어떻게 준비하나요?
There are still some procedures to go.
아직 몇 가지 절차가 남아 있습니다.
Almost complete.
거의 완료되었습니다.
Secret documents in Zhao An's safe
자오안의 금고에 들어 있는 비밀 문서
It is written that there is Shan's plan.
Shan의 계획이 있다고 쓰여 있습니다.
It must have something to do with the Shan Project.
Shan 프로젝트와 관련이 있는 게 틀림없어요.
However, the Japanese shouldn't be
그러나 일본인은 이러면 안 된다.
directly gave this important document to Zhao An.
이 중요한 문서를 자오안에게 직접 전달했습니다.
Jadi, dokumen Zhao An
Jadi, dokumen Zhao An
or a subplan of the Shan Project?
아니면 Shan 프로젝트의 하위 계획인가요?
If it goes according to your plan,
계획대로 진행된다면,
Once the funds have been collected,
자금이 모아지면,
how long should I wait?
언제까지 기다려야 하나요?
And Kimura's dissatisfaction with Zhao An
그리고 조안에 대한 기무라의 불만
the amount of funds collected
모은 자금의 양
So, this plan...
그럼 이 계획은...
Maybe a funding plan for the Shan Project.
어쩌면 Shan 프로젝트에 대한 자금 조달 계획일 수도 있습니다.
Tomorrow I'm going to Nanjing,
내일은 난징으로 갑니다.
a week later returned.
일주일 뒤에 돌아왔다.
Take your new plan,
새로운 계획을 세워보세요.
Come with me to attend the special meeting.
저와 함께 특별 회의에 참석해 주세요.
After Kimura returned to Shanghai,
기무라가 상하이로 돌아온 후,
will attend a special meeting.
특별 모임에 참석하게 됩니다.
Maybe related to Shan's project.
어쩌면 Shan의 프로젝트와 관련이 있을 수도 있습니다.
Looks like that plan...
그런 계획인 것 같은데...
Maybe a breakthrough to investigate the Shan project.
Shan 프로젝트를 조사하는 획기적인 방법이 될 수도 있습니다.
However, these few days Zhao An disappeared without a trace.
그러나 며칠 전부터 자오안은 흔적도 없이 사라졌다.
There was absolutely no chance of getting close to him.
그와 가까워질 가능성은 전혀 없었다.
But the temporary budget that Lu Fang said
하지만 Lu Fang이 말한 임시 예산은
there may be instructions related to a special meeting.
특별 회의와 관련된 지시가 있을 수 있습니다.
Tomorrow you have to think of a way
내일은 방법을 생각해 봐야 해
look at the interim budget
임시예산을 봐
Good.
좋은.
Hello, Jia Ping.
안녕하세요, 지아핑님.
After work,
퇴근 후,
we went to the wedding dress shop next to the Yong'an shop.
용안 가게 옆에 있는 웨딩드레스 가게에 갔어요.
To see the wedding attire.
웨딩드레스를 보러 갑니다.
After work,
퇴근 후,
hey!
여기요!
I'm here.
나는 여기 있다.
Okay
좋아요
we met at the wedding dress shop after work.
우리는 퇴근 후 웨딩드레스 샵에서 만났습니다.
Good
좋은
until found.
발견될 때까지.
Fang
송곳니
luFang
루팡
Where do you want to go?
어디로 가고 싶나요?
I went to the Finance Bureau.
나는 재무국에 갔다.
That...
저것...
In a hurry?
급히?
There is still time.
아직 시간이 있습니다.
What do you say?
당신은 무엇을 말합니까?
Aren't I going to marry Zuo Shuang Tao?
나는 Zuo Shuang Tao와 결혼하지 않을 것인가?
Have to choose a wedding dress.
웨딩드레스를 선택해야 합니다.
Help me see.
볼 수 있도록 도와주세요.
Why look for Miss Zuo?
Miss Zuo를 찾는 이유는 무엇입니까?
why are you looking for me?
왜 나를 찾고 있나요?
My vision is problematic.
내 시력에 문제가 있습니다.
Want you to give me some advice.
나에게 조언을 좀 해주셨으면 합니다.
Next time I'll treat you to a meal.
다음에는 식사 대접을 할게요.
Twice.
두 배.
Can agree.
동의할 수 있습니다.
Still not fast?
아직도 빠르지 않나요?
Then go
그럼 가
tuan
투안
the bride is so beautiful,
신부가 너무 아름답습니다.
definitely looks good wearing anything.
확실히 뭘 입어도 예쁠 것 같아요.
This little girl is really good at talking.
이 어린 소녀는 말을 정말 잘해요.
Look how clever he is.
그가 얼마나 영리한지보세요.
Nona,
노나,
Do not take it wrong.
잘못 받아들이지 마십시오.
This lady is not a bride.
이 여자는 신부가 아닙니다.
This also can't blame the little girl.
이것도 어린 소녀를 비난할 수는 없습니다.
You said there is someone like me
나 같은 사람도 있다고 했잖아
can still accompany you.
여전히 당신과 동행할 수 있습니다.
Choosing a wedding dress for someone else
다른 사람을 위해 웨딩드레스를 선택하는 방법
how about this one?
이건 어때?
This is the latest model of our shop.
이것은 우리 가게의 최신 모델입니다.
If you like it, try it.
당신이 그것을 좋아한다면, 그것을 시도하십시오.
I don't want to.
나는 원하지 않는다.
Must try.
꼭 해봐.
However, what you tried was...
그러나 당신이 시도한 것은 ...
That model suits your aura better.
그 모델이 당신의 아우라에 더 잘 어울리네요.
Why should I try?
왜 노력해야 합니까?
Don't know when to get married.
언제 결혼할지 모르겠어요.
Your words are not true.
당신의 말은 사실이 아닙니다.
Women do not wear wedding dresses for men.
여성은 남성을 위해 웨딩드레스를 입지 않습니다.
Maintain your own beauty.
자신의 아름다움을 유지하세요.
True, or not?
사실인가요, 아닌가요?
Moreover
게다가
we're here.
여기에 있었다.
Try.
노력하다.
Nona.
노나.
Find suitable clothes for this Miss.
이 미스에게 어울리는 옷을 찾아보세요.
That style.
그 스타일.
Good.
좋은.
Come on, give me the bag.
자, 가방을 나에게 주세요.
Quick, go try it.
빨리 가서 시도해 보세요.
If so, I'll try.
그렇다면 시도해 보겠습니다.
Try.
노력하다.
Mari, Nona.
마리, 노나.
Please come here
여기에 오세요
jia Ping
지아 핑
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Why come so early?
왜 이렇게 일찍 와?
Didn't we agree after work?
퇴근 후에 합의하지 않았나요?
I don't work.
나는 일하지 않습니다.
So want to come early.
그래서 일찍 오고 싶다.
In fact, you
사실 당신은
Why didn't you come earlier and tell me?
왜 더 일찍 와서 나에게 말하지 않았나요?
Jia Ping
지아 핑
ping house
핑 하우스
Ping family
핑 가족
chen Jia Ping
첸 지아 핑
shouldn't you explain it to me?
나한테 설명하면 안 돼?
It does have to be explained
그것은 설명되어야만 한다
what needs to be explained?
무엇을 설명해야 합니까?
Jia Ping, accompany me to choose a wedding dress.
Jia Ping, 나와 함께 웨딩 드레스를 선택하세요.
So, here it is
자, 여기 있습니다
bukan, Lu Fang
북칸, 루팡
we can't storm like this.
우리는 이렇게 폭풍우를 일으킬 수 없습니다.
I actually
나는 실제로
Didn't we agree after work?
퇴근 후에 합의하지 않았나요?
come to the wedding dress shop to choose a wedding dress.
웨딩드레스 매장에 오셔서 웨딩드레스를 고르세요.
I just want to ask Lu Fang for help
Lu Fang에게 도움을 요청하고 싶습니다.
give me advice?
조언 좀 해줄래?
Don't get me wrong.
오해하지 마세요.
My wedding dress doesn't need to be chosen by someone else.
내 웨딩 드레스는 다른 사람이 선택할 필요가 없습니다.
Don't.
하지 않다.
I was wrong, I was
내가 틀렸어, 내가 그랬어
jia Ping
지아 핑
today's problem
오늘의 문제
it's you who's not right.
옳지 않은 건 바로 당신이에요.
Let alone the angry Shuang Tao,
화난 Shuang Tao는 물론이고,
I'm also very angry.
나도 매우 화가 났다.
Maybe you asked me to accompany you
어쩌면 당신은 나에게 동행을 요청했을 수도 있습니다
choose a wedding dress for your bride.
신부를 위한 웨딩드레스를 선택하세요.
What do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
Correct.
옳은.
It's all my fault.
그것은 모두 내 잘못이야.
My judgment is not good.
내 판단은 좋지 않다.
Sorry you two
미안해 너희 둘
you should have told me,
나한테 말했어야 했는데,
so that I come early.
그래서 일찍 오려고요.
Good.
좋은.
Guoguo, whatever you say is right.
Guoguo, 당신이 말하는 것은 무엇이든 옳습니다.
Actually...
실제로...
Actually there is no other meaning
사실 다른 뜻은 없어요
I just want when you come,
난 단지 당신이 언제 오길 바랄 뿐이에요.
I can show off
뽐낼 수 있어요
in front of you.
당신의 앞에.
Like this.
이와 같이.
Two peaches?
복숭아 두 개?
Don't be angry anymore.
더 이상 화내지 마세요.
Jia Ping
지아 핑
he also has good intentions
그 사람도 좋은 의도가 있어
everything is being considered for you.
모든 것이 당신을 위해 고려되고 있습니다.
During the journey here, he kept talking to me,
여기까지 여행하는 동안 그는 나에게 계속해서 말을 걸었다.
must choose the most beautiful wedding dress for you.
당신에게 가장 아름다운 웨딩드레스를 선택해야 합니다.
Today is a happy day.
오늘은 행복한 날입니다.
Don't think too much.
너무 많이 생각하지 마십시오.
Let's see.
어디 보자.
What about the wedding dress on my body?
내 몸에 입는 웨딩드레스는 어떨까요?
Quite good.
꽤 좋은.
Very suitable for you.
당신에게 매우 적합합니다.
No.
아니요.
This way
이 방법
matches your aura.
당신의 아우라와 일치합니다.
That's right, right?
그렇죠?
Guoguo, look at that one.
궈궈, 저거 좀 봐.
That's the one at the front.
앞쪽에 있는 것이 바로 그 것입니다.
That one's good.
그거 좋은데.
You try that one.
당신은 그것을 시도합니다.
Nona,
노나,
please find the right size for my girlfriend.
내 여자친구에게 꼭 맞는 사이즈를 찾아주세요.
Good.
좋은.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
That...
저것...
Mari, Nona.
마리, 노나.
Please
제발
fang
송곳니
thank you, thank you
고마워요, 고마워요
three times
세 번
eat three times?
세 번 먹나요?
I saw your emergency contact sign
네 비상연락처 표시를 봤어
see your emergency contact sign
비상 연락처 표시를 확인하세요
immediately rushed here
당장 여기로 달려갔다
your and Chen Jiaping's wedding
당신과 천자핑의 결혼식
must be implemented within three days
3일 이내에 시행해야 함
Why?
왜?
Just got the information.
방금 정보를 얻었습니다.
Next week the Shan Xia soldiers will be transferred
다음 주에 Shan Xia 병사들이 이송될 예정입니다
Military Police Soldier commander Su Zhou.
헌병대 사령관 소저우(Su Zhou).
Next Monday will leave.
다음주 월요일은 출발합니다.
If your wedding is held after that,
그 이후에 결혼식을 올리게 된다면
he didn't have time to attend.
그는 참석할 시간이 없었습니다.
All our plans failed.
우리의 모든 계획은 실패했습니다.
Is time too tight?
시간이 너무 빡빡한가요?
in a hurry?
급히?
Do you really take this marriage seriously?
정말 이 결혼을 진지하게 받아들이시나요?
The important thing was to let the Shan Xia soldiers attend.
중요한 것은 산샤 병사들을 참석시키는 것이었다.
Isn't that so?
그렇지 않나요?
Correct.
옳은.
So you decide quickly
그러니까 빨리 결정해
time and place of the wedding party.
결혼식 시간과 장소.
And also your action plan.
그리고 당신의 행동 계획도요.
So I can make an evacuation plan after surgery.
그래서 수술 후 대피 계획을 세울 수 있습니다.
Do you still have other worries?
아직도 다른 걱정이 있나요?
No.
아니요.
Nona Zuo,
노나 주오,
Mr. Chen said if you don't see it,
첸 씨는 만약 당신이 그것을 보지 못한다면,
he won't go.
그는 가지 않을 것이다.
Good.
좋은.
Maksudku Guoguo.
Maksudku Guoguo.
I was wrong, okay?
내가 틀렸어, 알았지?
forgive me
용서 해줘
You see.
알다시피.
I've bought the wedding dress you like
네가 좋아하는 웨딩드레스를 샀어
at that time, I will let you wear it.
그때는 입게 해줄게.
So I took you dancing
그래서 난 당신을 춤추게 했어요
this one is for Lu Fang, right?
이건 Lu Fang을 위한 것 맞죠?
I'm telling you
나는 당신에게 말하고있다
no one can match you.
그 누구도 당신과 맞설 수 없습니다.
You are the most beautiful wearing this.
이것을 입는 당신이 가장 아름답습니다.
Whatever you wear is good.
무엇을 입든 좋습니다.
Signs.
표지판.
Beautiful.
아름다운.
Ugly as hell.
정말 못생겼어요.
You're the most beautiful.
당신은 가장 아름답습니다.
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
This?
이것?
Salted vegetable pickles.
소금에 절인 야채 피클.
Buy wedding dresses, hotels, buy furniture,
웨딩 드레스, 호텔 구매, 가구 구매,
all my savings are gone.
내 저축이 모두 사라졌습니다.
Someday you will marry me.
언젠가 당신은 나와 결혼할 거예요.
The two of us can only eat pickles to live.
우리 둘은 피클만 먹어도 살 수 있다.
If you want me to forgive you,
내가 당신을 용서해 주기를 원한다면,
You have to promise me one thing.
한 가지 약속해 주셔야 해요.
I will agree to whatever your terms are.
나는 당신의 조건이 무엇이든 동의할 것입니다.
Say it.
말해.
We have a wedding in three days.
우리는 3일 뒤에 결혼식이 있어요.
Three days?
삼 일?
Not.
아니다.
I didn't have time to prepare it
준비할 시간이 없었어요
you won't agree anymore.
당신은 더 이상 동의하지 않을 것입니다.
Don't, don't.
하지 마세요.
I agree, I agree.
동의합니다. 동의합니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Tomorrow morning I will go look for a hotel, how about it?
내일 아침에 호텔을 찾으러 갈 건데 어때요?
Do not be angry.
화 내지 마.
No need.
필요 없음.
I've found it.
나는 그것을 찾았습니다.
When passing by Sha Xun's villa today,
오늘 샤쉰의 별장을 지나갈 때,
I saw it was quite luxurious and magnificent there.
나는 그곳이 꽤 고급스럽고 웅장하다는 것을 보았습니다.
I like it very much.
나는 그것을 아주 많이 좋아.
It has been decided
결정되었습니다
I like it too.
나도 좋아해.
However, Guoguo, do you know?
하지만 Guoguo, 알고 있나요?
How much is Sha Xun villa?
샤쉰 빌라는 얼마인가요?
A banquet table,
연회 테이블,
it's equivalent to my monthly salary.
내 월급과 맞먹는다.
It turns out,
그것은 밝혀,
my weight in your heart.
당신 마음 속의 내 무게.
Still not enough.
아직 충분하지 않습니다.
Don't, don't.
하지 마세요.
Quite heavy.
꽤 무겁습니다.
Very heavy.
매우 무겁습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
I will pay the down payment tomorrow morning.
내일 아침에 계약금을 지불하겠습니다.
Put the dress down.
드레스를 내려 놓으세요.
You can go home first.
먼저 집에 가셔도 됩니다.
You don't want to see me?
나를보고 싶지 않아?
You did not know?
너는 몰랐다?
Three days before the wedding,
결혼식 3일 전,
the two brides and grooms cannot meet.
두 신랑신부가 만날 수 없습니다.
Good.
좋은.
Anyway, after you marry me, we both have to meet every day.
어쨌든 당신이 나와 결혼한 후에는 우리 둘 다 매일 만나야 해요.
Not another day.
다른 날이 아닙니다.
I go first.
내가 먼저 간다.
I'm really going yeah.
나 진짜 갈 거야 응.
Go away.
저리 가요.
Later, eat pickles with me, okay?
나중에 나랑 피클 먹자, 알았지?
Guoguo.
궈궈.
Your appearance when wearing a wedding dress
웨딩드레스를 입었을 때의 모습
when wearing a wedding dress.
웨딩드레스를 입었을 때.
Very beautiful.
매우 아름답습니다.
According to the information on the budget form,
예산 양식의 정보에 따르면,
a special meeting will be held in three days at two o'clock in the afternoon,
3일 후 오후 2시에 특별회의가 열릴 예정이며,
will be held at the Huihong building in Wanning Bridge.
Wanning Bridge의 Huihong 빌딩에서 개최됩니다.
Coincidentally, my wedding day was also the same.
공교롭게도 나의 결혼식 날도 마찬가지였다.
Maybe on the way Zhao An attended a meeting,
어쩌면 조안이 회의에 참석하는 길에,
can look for opportunities
기회를 찾을 수 있다
photographed the plan in his hand.
그의 손에 계획을 촬영했습니다.
Here.
여기.
Boss, where do you put it?
사장님, 어디에 두시나요?
Just put it here.
그냥 여기에 넣어두세요.
Here.
여기.
Release this.
이것을 풀어라.
Good.
좋은.
Thank you boss.
감사합니다 보스.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
How
어떻게
original French cherry wood
오리지널 프렌치 체리나무
floral patterned sofa.
꽃무늬 소파.
Perfect.
완벽한.
I only know to ask you to do something.
나는 당신에게 뭔가를 해달라고 요청할 줄만 압니다.
Correct.
옳은.
But
하지만
why is this sofa so green?
이 소파는 왜 초록색이야?
Is it green?
녹색인가요?
Green? How great?
녹색? 얼마나 대단한가요?
But...
하지만...
Not important, not important.
중요하지 않아요, 중요하지 않아요.
This...
이것...
Paper Money.
지폐.
Everyone's friends.
모두의 친구.
What banknotes?
무슨 지폐?
You can too.
당신도 할 수 있습니다.
These words come out of your mouth,
이런 말이 입에서 나오네요.
why do I sound so comfortable?
내 말은 왜 이렇게 편안해?
Tomorrow I still want to get married.
내일도 나는 결혼하고 싶다.
I also didn't say I wanted to ask for wedding money.
결혼금을 요구하고 싶다고도 말하지 않았습니다.
Are you treating me?
나를 치료하고 있습니까?
I really want to
나는 정말로하고 싶다
however, tomorrow everyone is a traitor.
그러나 내일은 모두가 배신자다.
You can drink comfortably,
편안하게 마실 수 있고,
that is true.
그것은 사실이다.
This time you called me here
이번엔 네가 나를 여기로 불러줬어
not just to make money, right?
단지 돈을 벌기 위해서가 아니죠?
Knocking you is not for profit anymore.
당신을 두드리는 것은 더 이상 이익을 위한 것이 아닙니다.
I already know.
나는 이미 알고 있다.
Like this,
이와 같이,
tomorrow at 1 pm
내일 오후 1시에
Zhao An's car will pass through the French concession
자오안의 자동차는 프랑스 조계지를 통과할 예정이다.
you have to think of a way
방법을 생각해야 해
help me stop this car
이 차를 멈출 수 있게 도와주세요
Then
그 다음에
then took him to the patrol room
그런 다음 그를 순찰실로 데려갔습니다.
and hold his belongings
그리고 그의 소지품을 보관하세요
waiting for the opportunity to take out the documents in his bag,
가방 속 서류를 꺼낼 기회를 기다리며,
and handed it to me.
그리고 그것을 나에게 건네주었습니다.
What document?
무슨 문서?
This is an important plan.
이것은 중요한 계획입니다.
I will immediately revise the contents of the plan,
즉시 계획 내용을 수정하겠습니다.
then you put the documents back into the bag.
그런 다음 서류를 다시 가방에 넣습니다.
Without realizing,
깨닫지도 못한 채,
get important information.
중요한 정보를 얻으세요.
Correct.
옳은.
So I have one question
그럼 질문이 하나 있어요
why are you so sure
왜 그렇게 확신해?
Zhao An's car will enter the French concession?
조안의 차가 프랑스 조계에 들어갈 것인가?
Enter from what level?
몇레벨부터 들어가나요?
When does it come in?
언제 들어오나요?
Which way?
어떤 방법으로?
For what reason am I holding him back?
내가 그를 붙잡고 있는 이유는 무엇일까?
That's why I said I wouldn't let you go.
그래서 내가 널 놓지 않겠다고 말한 거야.
Telling you to come together to discuss
같이 모여서 의논하자고 말함
how to solve this problem.
이 문제를 해결하는 방법.
Catch where?
어디에서 잡아?
Gambling place.
도박장.
How do you find clues?
단서는 어떻게 찾나요?
Where are the clues.
단서는 어디에 있습니까?
I just went to play for a while.
그냥 잠시 놀러 갔어요.
Unexpectedly, this child was also there.
의외로 이 아이도 거기에 있었습니다.
I saw it when I came in.
들어오자마자 봤네요.
Then when the boy found me,
그러다가 그 소년이 나를 발견했을 때,
he immediately ran away.
그는 즉시 도망쳤다.
I chased him like that.
나는 그 사람을 그렇게 쫓아다녔다.
I chased him for two blocks.
나는 그를 두 블록 동안 쫓아다녔다.
It has been confirmed that he was the perpetrator who killed the foot of the mountain
그가 산기슭을 죽인 가해자로 확인됐다.
Correct.
옳은.
I've confessed.
나는 고백했다.
Good.
좋은.
Say it.
말해.
I told you
내가 말했잖아
I am the murderer who killed the foot of the mountain
나는 산기슭을 죽인 살인자
I still want to say what
아직도 무슨 말을 하고 싶은데
who is your boss?
당신의 상사는 누구입니까?
Never seen.
본 적이 없다.
Do you still have one more person?
아직 한 사람 더 있나요?
There is one person named Da Xuan
Da Xuan이라는 사람이 있습니다.
Hasn't it been killed by you guys?
너희들이 죽인 게 아니지?
Still have
아직
There isn't any.
아무것도 없습니다.
You lie?
너 거짓말하는구나?
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
Give it back to me.
다시 돌려주세요.
What is the use of this number above?
위의 숫자는 무슨 용도인가요?
I ask you to return it to me
돌려달라고 부탁해요
on a pendant that is very important to you
당신에게 매우 중요한 펜던트에
there are numbers.
숫자가 있습니다.
So this number...
그럼 이 번호는...
It means unusual.
특이한 뜻입니다.
Under the mountain, he asks you
산 아래서 그가 당신에게 묻습니다.
what are you looking for?
무엇을 찾고 계신가요?
One of the perpetrators of the murder on the mountain
산에서 일어난 살인 사건의 가해자 중 한 명
has already been captured by our Zhao An.
이미 우리 Zhao An이 캡처했습니다.
So come report to Dassao at the foot of the mountain.
그러니 산기슭에 있는 다사오에게 보고하십시오.
What does it mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Report, Commander under the mountain.
보고하세요, 사령관님, 산 아래로.
On the day I interrogated the left twin peaches,
왼쪽 쌍둥이 복숭아를 심문하던 날,
never asked him to fill in personal data.
그에게 개인 데이터를 입력하라고 요청한 적이 없습니다.
I remember,
기억해,
the date of birth he filled in
그가 작성한 생년월일
is September 17th.
9월 17일이에요.
You mean, it's the Zuo Twins' birthday?
오늘이 Zuo Twins의 생일이라는 거죠?
Correct.
옳은.
Is Kun the one you caught
쿤이 네가 잡은 거야?
familiar with Shuang Tao left.
Shuang Tao에 대해 잘 알고 있습니다.
I think not only know,
제 생각엔 아는 것 뿐만 아니라,
maybe he likes the left twin's peaches.
아마도 그는 왼쪽 쌍둥이의 복숭아를 좋아할 것입니다.
Otherwise, how can you engrave birthdays
그렇지 않으면 어떻게 생일을 새길 수 있겠습니까?
on your own necklace pendant?
당신의 목걸이 펜던트에?
You continue.
계속하세요.
Prince of the mountains
산의 왕자
when you were murdered at the train station,
당신이 기차역에서 살해당했을 때,
suspicion of left twin
왼쪽 쌍둥이 의심
not yet cancelled.
아직 취소되지 않았습니다.
Just because of Chen Jia Ping's evidence
Chen Jia Ping의 증거 때문에
so I didn't find any strong evidence
그래서 강력한 증거를 찾지 못했어요
to get them married
그 사람들을 결혼시키려고
isn't this also a trap?
이것도 함정 아닌가?
then lure the snake out of the hole?
그럼 뱀을 구멍 밖으로 유인해볼까?
This time I can catch Kun,
이번에는 쿤을 잡을 수 있겠네요.
I think I could hit it with one blow.
한 방에 쳐낼 수 있을 것 같아요.
Didn't you say that Kun swore to death he wouldn't confess?
쿤이 자백하지 않겠다고 목숨을 걸었다고 하지 않았나요?
In this man's heart,
이 사람의 마음에는
if you already have a woman you love,
이미 사랑하는 여자가 있다면,
just make him suffer a little,
그 사람을 좀 괴롭게 해주세요.
he wouldn't say a word
그 사람은 아무 말도 안 했을 거야
So, what way do you have?
그럼 어떤 방법이 있나요?
Isn't the left twin peach about to get married soon?
왼쪽 쌍둥이 복숭아도 곧 결혼을 앞둔거 아닌가요?
What do you think if Kun
쿤이라면 어떻게 생각하시나요?
see for yourself the woman you love
당신이 사랑하는 여자를 직접 만나보세요
will marry another man.
다른 남자와 결혼할 거예요.
How do you think it feels
어떤 느낌일 것 같아?
how does he feel?
그의 기분은 어떠 할까?
Car key.
자동차 열쇠.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Invite the bride and groom.
신랑 신부를 초대합니다.
Today is your big day.
오늘은 당신의 중요한 날입니다.
My car can't
내 차는 그럴 수 없어
too sorry
너무 미안해
He is the nephew of the Yu family after all,
그는 결국 유 가문의 조카이고,
must have self-respect.
자존심이 있어야 합니다.
Many styles.
많은 스타일.
Boss Yu has already arranged everything,
유 사장은 이미 모든 것을 준비했고,
can also
또한 할 수 있다
Jia Ping
지아 핑
That means Boss Yu attaches great importance to you
이는 Yu Boss가 당신을 매우 중요하게 생각한다는 것을 의미합니다.
in the future we will be even higher.
앞으로 우리는 더욱 높아질 것입니다.
Height.
키.
Here.
여기.
Very delighted.
매우 기뻤습니다.
Sis,
언니,
today the meeting has finished.
오늘 회의가 끝났습니다.
Chen Jia Ping's wedding at night
Chen Jia Ping의 밤 결혼식
are you still going?
아직도 가니?
Of course.
물론.
Tonight there will be a good show.
오늘 밤에는 좋은 쇼가 있을 거예요.
Is it true?
사실인가요?
Do you want to lie against the wall tonight and hear the word bed?
오늘 밤 벽에 기대어 누워서 침대라는 말을 듣고 싶나요?
Do you think I'm you?
내가 너라고 생각하니?
Sis.
언니.
When can I drink your wedding beer?
결혼식 맥주는 언제 마실 수 있나요?
When do you go for treatment?
언제 치료받으러 가나요?
I'm not sick.
나는 아프지 않다.
When compared with everything,
모든 것과 비교했을 때,
do you feel you are normal?
당신은 당신이 정상이라고 생각합니까?
Your questions and your way of thinking,
당신의 질문과 사고방식,
Just normal
그냥 평범
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
I'll go take a look.
나는 가서 살펴볼 것이다.
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Soon, soon, Sis.
곧, 곧, 언니.
There's no time anymore.
더 이상 시간이 없습니다.
By the way Meg
그런데 메그
That's a French concession
그건 프랑스의 양보야
Sis, you've forgotten
언니, 잊으셨어요?
the suffering we experienced before
우리가 이전에 겪은 고통
we don't have an entry card.
우리는 출입카드가 없어요.
Meg Street is in the westernmost part
메그 스트리트는 가장 서쪽에 있어요
Concession patrols rarely patrol there.
양보 순찰대는 그곳을 거의 순찰하지 않습니다.
But it's a long way
하지만 길이 멀다
leave.
떠나다.
Stop the car! Stop!
차를 세워! 멈추다!
Sis.
언니.
Didn't you say there are no patrols on this road?
이 길에는 순찰대가 없다고 하지 않았나요?
Abnormal
이상
chief detective
수석 형사
ketua Zhao
케투아 자오
luck
운
very compatible.
매우 호환됩니다.
I'm sorry,
죄송합니다,
common problem
일반적인 문제
you have to check your concession permit
양보 허가를 확인해야합니다
Good
좋은
borrowing the way
길을 빌리다
Excuse me
실례합니다
Thank you inspector
감사합니다 검사님
go
가다
Wait a while.
잠시만 기다려주세요.
There is no entry permit letter,
입국허가서가 없고,
even tried to bribe employees
직원들에게 뇌물을 주려고도 했고
I now suspect you of French concessions
나는 이제 당신이 프랑스의 양보를 의심합니다
have bad intentions
나쁜 의도를 갖고 있다
guard,
경비원,
take them down
그들을 내려
check the body.
몸을 확인해 보세요.